<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About CS-EJ4104 (Introduction to DevOps) on Hugo static website for Intro to DevOps</title>
    <link>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About CS-EJ4104 (Introduction to DevOps) on Hugo static website for Intro to DevOps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 21:22:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Csej</title>
      <link>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/csej/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 21:22:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/csej/</guid>
      <description>About cs-ej4104 (Introduction to DevOps) Some reasons to choose Introduction to DevOps course: Why DevOps? DevOps is collaboration between Development, Operations and other teams, trying to achieve business goals. The concept was started around 2009 and DevOps practice can give you great advantages. F.ex. Deploy 30 times more frequently and 200 times faster, with 60 % fewer disruptions and recover 168 times faster when failure is experienced. Leading to more profitable companies &amp;amp; higher job satisfaction!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cs-ej4104</title>
      <link>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/cs-ej4104/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 21:22:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/cs-ej4104/</guid>
      <description>About CS-EJ4104 (Introduction to DevOps) Some reasons to choose Introduction to DevOps course: Why DevOps? DevOps is collaboration between Development, Operations and other teams, trying to achieve business goals. The concept was started around 2009 and DevOps practice can give you great advantages. F.ex. Deploy 30 times more frequently and 200 times faster, with 60 % fewer disruptions and recover 168 times faster when failure is experienced. Leading to more profitable companies &amp;amp; higher job satisfaction!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning DevOps</title>
      <link>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/learningdevops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 21:08:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/learningdevops/</guid>
      <description>Learning DevOps Here are some thoughts on the topic of learning on the course CS-EJ4104. The were many topics that were mentioned, and I will only mention a few. Also some of my own thoughts on things that I found tricky or easy.
 This was a good introduction to DevOps in my mind. The videos were very to the point, and I feel that they gave a good overview of CAMS and continuous improvement and the ways to achieve it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 22:03:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/about/</guid>
      <description>About CS-EJ4104 (Introduction to DevOps)  Some reasons to choose Introduction to DevOps course: Why DevOps? DevOps is collaboration between Development, Operations and other teams, trying to achieve business goals. The concept was started around 2009 and DevOps practice can give you great advantages. F.ex. Deploy 30 times more frequently and 200 times faster, with 60 % fewer disruptions and recover 168 times faster when failure is experienced. Leading to more profitable companies &amp;amp; higher job satisfaction!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>learned devops</title>
      <link>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 22:03:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cs-ej4104-fall-2020.github.io/heidiali-project/post/learning/</guid>
      <description>Learned devops Here are some thoughts on the topic of learning on the course CS-EJ4104. The were many topics that were mentioned, and I will only mention a few. Also some of my own thoughts on things that I found tricky or easy.
 This was a good introduction to DevOps in my mind. The videos were very to the point, and I feel that they gave a good overview of CAMS and continuous improvement and the ways to achieve it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
